The legend. The battle. The first hero.
10,000 BC is a adventure, action, drama film directed by Roland Emmerich.
A prehistoric epic that follows a young mammoth hunter's journey through
uncharted territory to secure the future of his tribe.
D’Leh, played by Steven Strait.
Evolet, played by Camilla Belle.
Tic-Tic, played by Cliff Curtis.
Baku, played by Nathanael Baring.
Ka’Ren, played by Mo Zinal.
Warlord, played by Affif Ben Badra.
10,000 BC is a 2008 American action-adventure film, directed by Roland
Emmerich, and written by Emmerich and Harald Kloser.
The cast includes Steven Strait, Camilla Belle, and Cliff Curtis.
The film depicts the journeys of a prehistoric tribe of mammoth hunters.
10,000 BC premiered at Potsdamer Platz on February 10,
2008, and was released by Warner Bros.
Pictures on March 7.
It received negative reviews from critics and grossed
$270 million against a $105M budget.
The film explores themes of hunter, indigenous, fighter, female lover, pyramid.
The tone is emotional.